(Leonard:)So... when you say
(Leonard:)you're not going
to freak out about the DVD,
(Leonard:)here's what that means.
(Leonard:)Don't fixate on it,
(Leonard:)don't wake me up
in the middle of the night,
(Leonard:)or nag me through the door
while I'm on the toilet.
(Sheldon:)Okay, first, talking to you
while you're on the toilet
(Sheldon:)isn't exactly a picnic for me either.
(Sheldon:)Remember, when you can hear me,
I can hear you.
(Sheldon:)And, second,
you completely disregard
(Sheldon:)how uncomfortable
unresolved issues are for me.
It's like, an itch in my brain
I can't scratch.
(Leonard:)When I broke my arm I used
to stick a coat hanger down there.
(Leonard:)You ever try that?
Maybe go in through the ear?
(Sheldon:)You wouldn't make jokes
if you could feel the way I feel.
(Leonard:)Well, I don't know how to do that.
(Sheldon:)How about this?
(Sheldon:)I promise I won't pester you
about the DVD.